<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing</title>
    <link>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/</link>
    <description>I wanted a category to share what I learn about writing. So i can improve my writing skills and become a better thinker and better at helping others.&#xA;Things I Learned from Dickie Bush and Nicolas Cole’s Writing Email Course </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>19 Biggest Lessons From Reading 100 Books</title>
      <link>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/19-biggest-lessons-from-reading-100-books./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/19-biggest-lessons-from-reading-100-books./</guid>
      <description>I started reading non-fiction after hitting my rock bottom. I found people to look up to and saw that they were reading and learning constantly to better themselves. This inspired me to develop a reading and self improvement habit that I have continued for more than 10 years.&#xA;No single book has the ability to change your life. But the things you do, good or bad, over time, compound to extraordinary changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Ways to Quit Caffeine</title>
      <link>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/4-ways-to-quit-caffeine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/4-ways-to-quit-caffeine/</guid>
      <description>The cycle of caffeine addiction can be vicious. Just like any other drug.&#xA;The cycle goes like this:&#xA;Caffeine causes a variety of pains and withdrawal symptoms. &gt; You use caffeine to relieve these pains and withdrawal symptoms. &gt; Caffeine causes pains and withdrawal symptoms.&#xA;Unless you can break this pattern. You will be trapped in this cycle forever. How do you break the cycle?&#xA;Here are 4 options for breaking the cycle. Along with the benefits and drawbacks for each.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Steps to Get Back on a NoFap Streak Immediately</title>
      <link>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/7-steps-to-get-back-on-a-nofap-streak-immediately/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/7-steps-to-get-back-on-a-nofap-streak-immediately/</guid>
      <description> Reconnect with your reason why. Is there a book or YouTube video that explained the benefits. What motivated you to start in the first place? Write down the negatives associated with porn and masturbation. And the benefits you have felt from previous attempts.&#xA;Set a goal related to nofap. A 90 day timeline is far enough to make real progress. But not so far out that your timeline is unpredictable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caffeine is Destroying You</title>
      <link>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/caffeine-is-destroying-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/caffeine-is-destroying-you/</guid>
      <description>Look at this bird.&#xA;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HUngLgGRJpo&#xA;Any substance that gives you a lift follows the same journey as the bird in the video. You start out at a healthy balance. But before you know it. You are trapped in an addictive cycle.&#xA;DISCLAIMER: YOU MAY NOT FEEL ANY NEGATIVES OF CAFFEINE UNTIL YEARS OF USE!!&#xA;Or.. you may not associate the negatives that are currently happening with caffeine. This is because there is a disconnect with the immediate response to caffeine and the negatives it brings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nat Eliason&#39;s SEO course</title>
      <link>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/nat-eliasons-seo-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://davidvargas.xyz/writing/nat-eliasons-seo-course/</guid>
      <description>Things I learned for Nat Eliason’s SEO Course Leveling up&#xA;Start with an easy keyword Over time, adjust article for harder and harder keywords Long tail keywords with low competition Can change meta title for google to the harder keyword later Can only change the meta title unless there is something the content is missing that the broader keyword asks for. At first, pick something under 5,000 searches You don’t need to spend time building backlinks. You can rank for keywords that aren’t even IN your articles. You don’t need to focus on keyword density. Focus on intent.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>