<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Writing off the Cuff</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/writing-off-the-cuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/writing-off-the-cuff/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My favorite and by far easiest method of writing is writing off the cuff. You get your thoughts down and spring new thoughts to life. You are finding out what you know without referencing materials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are creating out of nothing. It is pure writing and creativity folded into one. We all have a “Muse” that will give to us whenever we ask.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All you have to do is start writing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/19-biggest-lessons-from-reading-100-books./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/19-biggest-lessons-from-reading-100-books./</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started reading non-fiction after hitting my rock bottom. I found people to look up to and saw that they were reading and learning constantly to better themselves. This inspired me to develop a reading and self improvement habit that I have continued for more than 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No single book has the ability to change your life. But the things you do, good or bad, over time, compound to extraordinary changes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/7-steps-to-get-back-on-a-nofap-streak-immediately/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/7-steps-to-get-back-on-a-nofap-streak-immediately/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reconnect with your reason why. Is there a book or YouTube video that explained the benefits. What motivated you to start in the first place? Write down the negatives associated with porn and masturbation. And the benefits you have felt from previous attempts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set a goal related to nofap. A 90 day timeline is far enough to make real progress. But not so far out that your timeline is unpredictable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/austerities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/austerities/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are austerities you should avoid all together. Such as any poison to the body. (Drugs, alcohol, caffeine, etc.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There may be drugs or chemicals perscribed by a doctor that are life saving. Choose your doctor wisely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other austerities should be used or enjoyed. But periodically given up. Both as a test of suffering, and to open up other doors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;p&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/caffeine-and-weightloss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/caffeine-and-weightloss/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Any claim you make regarding caffeine is going to be filled with hot takes. For example, I could say that quitting caffeine should, in theory, promote healthy testosterone levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The immediate response from many would be: &amp;ldquo;There is no scientific evidence for this.&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Actually, here is a study showing caffeine use spikes testosterone levels.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when you think of the time frame for most caffeine studies, your looking at around 1 day to no more than a few weeks. But we lack long term studies of people who have given up the bean and moved on to a healthier lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/caffeine-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/caffeine-bird/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No seriously. Look at this bird.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HUngLgGRJpo&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HUngLgGRJpo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any substance that gives you a lift follows the same journey as the bird in the video. You start out at a healthy balance. But before you know it. You are trapped in an addictive cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DISCLAIMER: YOU MAY NOT FEEL ANY NEGATIVES OF CAFFEINE UNTIL YEARS OF USE!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or.. you may not associate the negatives that are currently happening with caffeine. This is because there is a disconnect with the immediate response to caffeine and the negatives it brings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/how-i-earned-my-first-penny-on-medium.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/how-i-earned-my-first-penny-on-medium.com/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boys and girls..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We made it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your looking at a new professional writer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One who has finally earned money writing online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;davidvargasxyz.github.io/docs/images/Pasted%20image%2020240521051800.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may not look like much. A penny? You ask.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not just a penny. This is a seed. The acorn of FREEDOM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may not be able to do much with this penny. But boy oh boy does this feed something greater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It feeds an idea.&#39;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/my-journey-with-addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/my-journey-with-addiction/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2010, I was facing felony charges for distribution of drugs. I was a drug addict. Hook line and sinker. But never admitted that to myself. My drug of choice? Anything I could get my hands on. Cocaine, ecstasy, weed, Xanax, Oxycontin, ciggys, alcohol, ativan, seroquil, spice, mushrooms.. You name it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/full%20(3).jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Desperately wanting to avoid prison time, I did whatever I could to turn my life around. The potential pain in carrying on was too great to tolerate. This was my rock bottom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/nat-elisons-seo-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/nat-elisons-seo-course/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Leveling up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start with an easy keyword&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over time, adjust article for harder and harder keywords&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long tail keywords with low competition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can change meta title for google to the harder keyword later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can only change the meta title unless there is something the content is missing that the broader keyword asks for.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At first, pick something under 5,000 searches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t need to spend time building backlinks.
You can rank for keywords that aren&amp;rsquo;t even IN your articles. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to focus on keyword density. Focus on intent.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/the-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/the-journey/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The journey you are on is about self discovery, growth, and redemption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are on the path. Do not cling to the past or in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not rush it. Experience your surroundings. Fill every moment with greatness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your pains today lead to solutions for the world forever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/things-i-learned-from-dickie-bush-and-nicolas-coles-writing-email-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/things-i-learned-from-dickie-bush-and-nicolas-coles-writing-email-course/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I went through Dickie Bush and Nicolas Cole&amp;rsquo;s email course on writing online. This course was great overall. Short and concise and has given me the motivation, by providing good reasons, to commit to consistently writing online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are my key takeaways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;10-problems-beginner-writers-face&#34;&gt;10 Problems beginner writers face.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Distractions (Write about them if you have to)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over-editing (Spend your first year focusing on ideas)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perfectionism (Create junk!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Procrastination (Get back in the boat before you drown)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-confidence (Build confidence by writing a ton)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generating Ideas (Use the Endless Idea Generator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Impostor Syndrome (Figure out how you can be different, not better)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing consistently (Consistency &amp;gt; talent)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choosing a platform (Medium, Twitter, Quora, LinkedIn, Typeshare)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finding time to write (You don&amp;rsquo;t find time, you make it)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;find-out-your-why-here-are-some-benefits-of-writing-online&#34;&gt;Find out your why. Here are some benefits of writing online.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Builds self confidence and clarifies the way that you see the world. Committing to something day after day spills into other areas of your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The more you write, the more ideas you uncover.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are scaling yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities come to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect to leaders because you become a leader yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-you-shouldnt-start-a-blog&#34;&gt;Why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start a blog.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no distribution flywheel. The algorithm serves your content to a few readers, if those readers engage with your content, then it can take off.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/writing-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/writing-on-twitter/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why is writing on Twitter worth it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you write a post that resonates with people. it can go viral because of the Twitter flywheel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A blog has no loop or algorithm to help you gain traction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4 Elements to a Twitter thread:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead-in Tweet (Hook the reader, What do they get by reading the rest of the thread?)
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headline and first sentence combined&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who is it for?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is it about?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why should they trust you?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What will the reader &amp;ldquo;get&amp;rdquo; in exchange?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How is their life going to be different after they read?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The 6 proven first-sentence formulas: • A moment in time • A controversial opinion • A vulnerable statement • A weight, unique insight • A strong declarative sentence • A thought-provoking question&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So avoid things like: • &amp;ldquo;Most&amp;rdquo; • &amp;ldquo;I think&amp;rdquo; • &amp;ldquo;Maybe&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Main Points&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TL;DR Recap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CTA (Collect their email, send them to your site, show them more of your content, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Ways to Quit Caffeine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/4-ways-to-quit-caffeine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/4-ways-to-quit-caffeine/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The cycle of caffeine addiction can be vicious. Just like any other drug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cycle goes like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caffeine causes a variety of pains and withdrawal symptoms. &amp;gt; You use caffeine to relieve these pains and withdrawal symptoms. &amp;gt; Caffeine causes pains and withdrawal symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless you can break this pattern. You will be trapped in this cycle forever. How do you break the cycle?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are 4 options for breaking the cycle. Along with the benefits and drawbacks for each.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
